in the back. First down and 10. And the
call here, Puny with the block and he's
GOING TO TAKE IT IN FOR THE TOUCHDOWN.
>> WELL, this has been a problem all season
long. It's not this initial contact.
It's the fact that they're not able to
wrap him up and limit it to that. It's
it's the the extended plays.
>> Robinson breaks the tackle AND HE'S IN.
TOUCHDOWN SAN FRANCISCO.
Power back one-on-one. There's Lamman in
the hole. It's all you can ask for on
defense.
>> Doesn't seem like that tall of an order
to come back from. Dylan to Robinson.
Boy, he's slippery. And here he goes
furbling and out of bounds. Play
complimentary football. The special
teams has to do their part which right
here Robinson breaks through a couple
tackles and works his way up near the 40
yd line. And after you played such a
good first half, they've got to finish
this half.
>> Robinson veering TO THE MIDDLE. BRIAN
ROBINSON JR. WHAT A RETURN AT a perfect
time.
>> Last week he was anticipating a lot of
run today. There's the pitch out. Brian
Robinson used check out there to block
and he finds a hole and THEN BROUGHT
DOWN MISEL.
Robinson on second and one. HE'S GOT THE
FIRST DOWN AND MORE AT THE 20 10 FIVE.
TOUCHDOWN.
Brian Robinson
to just get downhill. It's really easy
when you got two big cuz we used to call
them big fatties in front of you
creating space for yourself. Run for the
Super Bowl, but we'll see. Second down.
Robinson up the middle. Touchdown
Washington.
Second and goal. ROBINSON IN. TOUCHDOWN
WASHINGTON.
>> Need a half a yard for the first down
and into a crowd.
>> ROBINSON COMES OUT OF THE CROWD. BRIAN
ROBINSON JR. inside the 20 of the
Giants.
>> And he goes in the middle line of
scrimmage right here in the middle. Now
watch him just pop out. He gets hit,
pops out. Everybody thinks he's still in
the scrum.
>> There he goes.
>> It's almost like he hid and waited. Sam
Howell on the cusp of 300 yds passing in
this game. First down and more.
Robinson. ROBINSON. AND HE'S IN.
TOUCHDOWN.
>> THESE LAST COUPLE games look for him to
be a factor.
>> On second down, pressure comes. Howell's
in trouble. SPRINTS OUT AND FINDS
ROBINSON DOWN THE SIDELINE. AND ROBINSON
ON THE RUN. HE'S GOING TO TAKE IT ALL
THE WAY FOR A WASHINGTON TOUCHDOWN.
>> POWELL.
Plenty of time.
STOPPING THROWING TO THE END ZONE FOR
ROBINSON AND A TOUCHDOWN.
>> Robinson again hits THE HOLE HARD.
ROBINSON IS IN. TOUCHDOWN WASHINGTON.
TD percentage.
Second down and seven. ROBINSON TO THE
END ZONE. TOUCHDOWN.
Here's Robinson. Robinson cuts it up and
in for a Commander touchdown.
>> Powell running, THROWING CAUGHT.
TOUCHDOWN. It was bobbled at first, but
Robinson held on and Washington on
>> and he has Robinson wide open in the
flat and he kind of caught this thing
twice. He kind of bobbled it off his
chest and
here he is again.
HE JUST WON'T GO DOWN. TOUCHDOWN.
WHAT AN effort by Brian Robinson Jr.
>> And that is just sheer strength. Sam
Cosm, you're going to see he gets held
up here and Cosby number 76. He comes in
from behind and he starts moving the
pile and then with the re and goal.
Robinson
and he will get into the end zone for a
touchdown.